<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" />
  <updated>2023-05-07T15:12:33+00:00</updated>
  <id>/</id>
  <title type="html">XDAG | A new DAG-based cryptocurrency</title>
  <subtitle>A new DAG-based cryptocurrency</subtitle>
  <author>
      <name></name>
      <email></email>
  </author><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG 0.4.0 Go Wallet released</title>
      <link href="/2021/11/05/XDAG-Go-Wallet-0.4.0-officially-released.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG 0.4.0 Go Wallet released" />
      <published>2021-11-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2021-11-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2021/11/05/XDAG%20Go%20Wallet%200.4.0%20officially%20released</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2021/11/05/XDAG-Go-Wallet-0.4.0-officially-released.html">The new version of XDAG wallet (0.4.0) has been officially released.



XDAG’s community members can try to download 0.4.0 wallet with this link : https://github.com/XDagger/goXdagWallet/releases
0.4.0 the wallet has been adjusted in terms of design style, adding functions such as QR code, transfer address record,
conditional searching transfer details, improving compatibility and user experience.

This wallet have been developed by one of our long time supporter and developers Swordlet.
Community rewarded him 150000 XDAG for this good work, feel free to tip him on his adress to encourage him : 2muaPxu3kgDQX0MFzQEul3/7VLdnFay8

7. Bug bounty

If you find a bug, please visit[https://github.com/XDagger/goXdagWallet/issues/new/choose]
Submit a bug and leave your XDAG address. After we review, we will reward 1000XDAG to this address if a bug is found.

#####-By XDAG Community</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">The new version of XDAG wallet (0.4.0) has been officially released. XDAG’s community members can try to download 0.4.0 wallet with this link : https://github.com/XDagger/goXdagWallet/releases 0.4.0 the wallet has been adjusted in terms of design style, adding functions such as QR code, transfer address record, conditional searching transfer details, improving compatibility and user experience. This wallet have been developed by one of our long time supporter and developers Swordlet. Community rewarded him 150000 XDAG for this good work, feel free to tip him on his adress to encourage him : 2muaPxu3kgDQX0MFzQEul3/7VLdnFay8 7. Bug bounty If you find a bug, please visit[https://github.com/XDagger/goXdagWallet/issues/new/choose] Submit a bug and leave your XDAG address. After we review, we will reward 1000XDAG to this address if a bug is found. #####-By XDAG Community</summary></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG Mars Project</title>
      <link href="/2021/05/09/XDAG-Mars-plan.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG Mars Project" />
      <published>2021-05-09T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2021-05-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2021/05/09/XDAG-Mars-plan</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2021/05/09/XDAG-Mars-plan.html">XDAG Mars Project
        **to developers who aspire to develop**


1. Blockground introduction

XDAG take live in 2017 in the bitcointalk community, and is the first digital cryptocurrency based on DAG that can be mined using the PoW algorithm.
The XDAG network came go live in January 2018. There are no ICO, no pre-mining. The block reward is halved every four years. The  total volume is around 1.4 billion.

XDAG is currently being continuously developed and maintained by a group of developers who love blockchain and persist in the ideal of decentralization. 
The goal is to utilize the characteristics 
of DAG technology to create a high-speed, stable, and flexible blockchain technology that supports multiple main stream applications.

2.Technical advantages

1) XDAG is the first public chain based on DAG to realize the PoW.
Combining the high concurrency of DAG with the security and decentralization of POW to solve the “impossible triangle” problem in the blockchain technology;
2) Block = Transaction = Address.
 This unique design ensures that the transfer process will not lose coins due to typing in the wrong address; #### 3) Low transaction fee and high TPS. XDAG uses unique technology to solve many problems that may exist in the blockchain system, such as double-spending, uncontrollable transaction time, centralization, 34% attacks, and 51% attacks.


3.From Apollo Plan to Mars Plan

XDAG was highly respected once it was released, but in the first year of development, its own problems gradually exposed, such as the inability 
of the mining pool to synchronize and other serious problems, which made XDAG unable to continue its original glory.
On the one hand, mining tyrants relied on the cost advantages of FPGA and ASIC mining machines to “dig and sell”; on the other hand, the originalC code is in the low degree 
of engineering which makes programmers daunting.
XDAG entered the “darkest moment”. The low price of the currency and lack of development funds led to the slow development and entered a vicious circle.
At the critical moment in mid-2019, the XDAG community launched the Apollo Project for exploring a development path suitable for XDAG while ensuring the living space of XDAG.
Since that time, the XDAG community governance has gradually been on the right track, and XDAG has shown a good development trend. The release of the Java version is now near 
to complete. The RandomX algorithm upgrade was achieved with a big success, which solves the historical problems of the monopoly reward of mining tyrants and creates a much fair
 environment for participants. 
The RandomX algorithm allows users with ordinary PCs to participate in the mining process and obtain certain rewards easily, which has greatly increased users’ confidence in XDAG.
The success of Apollo’s Plan is not only due to the active maintenance of community developers, but also to the trust of all users in the development potential of XDAG.
The great success of the Apollo project is not only inseparable from the efforts of the XDAG community and fans, but also depends on the era of turbulent cryptocurrency.
 When Bitcoin, Ethereum, etc., have set new highs,and Coinbase landed on Nasdaq, the XDAG community launched the Mars project. The project will take XDAG forward a big step 
 on the basis of the achievements of the Apollo project, and open the way for eventually accommodating mainstream blockchain applications.

4. Outline of XDAG Mars Project

The Mars project is divided into four phases:

1. Exploration phase: XDAGJ testnet is online (online, in beta)
1) Construction of testnet: build a testnet with multiple mining pools, at least one C version mining pool and one Java version mining pool;
2) Test coin application: use mining reward distribution, users can mine to obtain test coin; or use issues to apply and distribute regularly;
3) Testnet access tutorial:complete tutorial of testnet mining, including the construction of miners, how to mine and the detailed introduction of miners’ command line;
4) Issues submission specification: the submission of bugs should describe detailed issues for quick analysis and resolution;
5) Blockchain browser: The most intuitive experience for users, you can use the block browser consistent with the official website;
6) Mining algorithm modification: access to RandomX algorithm;
7) Libp2p java version is added.

2. Landing phase: XDAGJ mainnet is online
1) Improve test cases: write test cases for existing functions;
2) Improve the log function: provide a relatively complete log service to facilitate trouble shooting;
3) Solve the various small problems of locally loading data, replace the recursive loading method with a loop to avoid stack overflow;
4) Realize the snapshot function: solve the problem of slow loading speed of the historical main block;
5) Mining function improvement: Consider replacing existing practices with more mature mining protocols, such as Stratum.

3. Expansion phase: XDAGJ smart contract is online
1) Use the Ethereum balance model to transform the data structure, remove the address block, and increase the handling fee;
2) Improve the existing public and private key and address generation methods, use BIPxx and other specifications, use the mnemonic scheme to generate public 
and private key pairs, and replace the wallet.dat method.
3) Lightweight wallet application to build metamask RPC compatible with web3;
4) Implement EVM that supports solidity language and is compatible with Ethereum smart contracts;
5) Remove whitelist.

4. Prosperity Phase: DAG-DEFI Infrastructure Development
1) Join the cross-chain scheme, compatible with the access of multiple blockchains, and realize the intercommunication between other chains and XDAG;
2) Join the oracle;
3) Join a distributed exchange.
The Mars project prioritizes the solution of technical issues that the community cares about. During this period, major research breakthroughs can be flexibly 
added to the development plan.

5. Time estimation


  
    
      1
      Phase
      Time(months)
      Difficulty
    
  
  
    
      2
      Exploration phase
      1-3
      Middle
    
    
      3
      Landing phase
      3-6
      High
    
    
      4
      Expansion phase
      3-6
      Very High
    
    
      5
      Prosperity phase
      1-6
      High
    
  


6. Donations
The development of XDAGJ is inseparable from the support of XDAG fans. I hope you will continue to support the development and testing of XDAGJ, and the developer team 
will return to the society with excellent code.[https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj#sponsorship].

As well you can also fund our main development wallets at this adress :
XDAG: FQglVQtb60vQv2DOWEUL7yh3smtj7g1s
BTC: 39QyFnyoW45dWMReaZtcoRHP2S4DqU8xQG
ETH: 0xb5F34fEb083186AfcB1DB1eFdE41eDA1f9BD9fB1

7. Bug bounty
After the XDAGJ testnet went live, in order to encourage community enthusiasts to participate in the construction of XDAGJ, a bug bounty hunter activity was launched. If you
 find a bug, please visit[https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/issues/new/choose]
Submit a bug and leave your XDAG address. After we review, we will reward 1000XDAG to this address if a bug is found.

8. Conclusion
Currently, XDAG has initially entered a stage of benign development. On the one hand, the Mars project plans the future development path of XDAG, gathers community forces, 
and promotes the evolution of XDAG to a new height; on the other hand, it uses the world’s number one Java programming language to improve the XDAG ecosystem, attract
 developers to join, and grow with the future king. Finally a prosperous scene of XDAG will be realized. The Mars project will also hold a number of activities to interact 
 with XDAG fans, so stay tuned.

-By XDAG Community</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">XDAG Mars Project **to developers who aspire to develop** 1. Blockground introduction XDAG take live in 2017 in the bitcointalk community, and is the first digital cryptocurrency based on DAG that can be mined using the PoW algorithm. The XDAG network came go live in January 2018. There are no ICO, no pre-mining. The block reward is halved every four years. The total volume is around 1.4 billion. XDAG is currently being continuously developed and maintained by a group of developers who love blockchain and persist in the ideal of decentralization. The goal is to utilize the characteristics of DAG technology to create a high-speed, stable, and flexible blockchain technology that supports multiple main stream applications. 2.Technical advantages 1) XDAG is the first public chain based on DAG to realize the PoW. Combining the high concurrency of DAG with the security and decentralization of POW to solve the “impossible triangle” problem in the blockchain technology; 2) Block = Transaction = Address. This unique design ensures that the transfer process will not lose coins due to typing in the wrong address; #### 3) Low transaction fee and high TPS. XDAG uses unique technology to solve many problems that may exist in the blockchain system, such as double-spending, uncontrollable transaction time, centralization, 34% attacks, and 51% attacks. 3.From Apollo Plan to Mars Plan XDAG was highly respected once it was released, but in the first year of development, its own problems gradually exposed, such as the inability of the mining pool to synchronize and other serious problems, which made XDAG unable to continue its original glory. On the one hand, mining tyrants relied on the cost advantages of FPGA and ASIC mining machines to “dig and sell”; on the other hand, the originalC code is in the low degree of engineering which makes programmers daunting. XDAG entered the “darkest moment”. The low price of the currency and lack of development funds led to the slow development and entered a vicious circle. At the critical moment in mid-2019, the XDAG community launched the Apollo Project for exploring a development path suitable for XDAG while ensuring the living space of XDAG. Since that time, the XDAG community governance has gradually been on the right track, and XDAG has shown a good development trend. The release of the Java version is now near to complete. The RandomX algorithm upgrade was achieved with a big success, which solves the historical problems of the monopoly reward of mining tyrants and creates a much fair environment for participants. The RandomX algorithm allows users with ordinary PCs to participate in the mining process and obtain certain rewards easily, which has greatly increased users’ confidence in XDAG. The success of Apollo’s Plan is not only due to the active maintenance of community developers, but also to the trust of all users in the development potential of XDAG. The great success of the Apollo project is not only inseparable from the efforts of the XDAG community and fans, but also depends on the era of turbulent cryptocurrency. When Bitcoin, Ethereum, etc., have set new highs,and Coinbase landed on Nasdaq, the XDAG community launched the Mars project. The project will take XDAG forward a big step on the basis of the achievements of the Apollo project, and open the way for eventually accommodating mainstream blockchain applications. 4. Outline of XDAG Mars Project The Mars project is divided into four phases: 1. Exploration phase: XDAGJ testnet is online (online, in beta) 1) Construction of testnet: build a testnet with multiple mining pools, at least one C version mining pool and one Java version mining pool; 2) Test coin application: use mining reward distribution, users can mine to obtain test coin; or use issues to apply and distribute regularly; 3) Testnet access tutorial:complete tutorial of testnet mining, including the construction of miners, how to mine and the detailed introduction of miners’ command line; 4) Issues submission specification: the submission of bugs should describe detailed issues for quick analysis and resolution; 5) Blockchain browser: The most intuitive experience for users, you can use the block browser consistent with the official website; 6) Mining algorithm modification: access to RandomX algorithm; 7) Libp2p java version is added. 2. Landing phase: XDAGJ mainnet is online 1) Improve test cases: write test cases for existing functions; 2) Improve the log function: provide a relatively complete log service to facilitate trouble shooting; 3) Solve the various small problems of locally loading data, replace the recursive loading method with a loop to avoid stack overflow; 4) Realize the snapshot function: solve the problem of slow loading speed of the historical main block; 5) Mining function improvement: Consider replacing existing practices with more mature mining protocols, such as Stratum. 3. Expansion phase: XDAGJ smart contract is online 1) Use the Ethereum balance model to transform the data structure, remove the address block, and increase the handling fee; 2) Improve the existing public and private key and address generation methods, use BIPxx and other specifications, use the mnemonic scheme to generate public and private key pairs, and replace the wallet.dat method. 3) Lightweight wallet application to build metamask RPC compatible with web3; 4) Implement EVM that supports solidity language and is compatible with Ethereum smart contracts; 5) Remove whitelist. 4. Prosperity Phase: DAG-DEFI Infrastructure Development 1) Join the cross-chain scheme, compatible with the access of multiple blockchains, and realize the intercommunication between other chains and XDAG; 2) Join the oracle; 3) Join a distributed exchange. The Mars project prioritizes the solution of technical issues that the community cares about. During this period, major research breakthroughs can be flexibly added to the development plan. 5. Time estimation 1 Phase Time(months) Difficulty 2 Exploration phase 1-3 Middle 3 Landing phase 3-6 High 4 Expansion phase 3-6 Very High 5 Prosperity phase 1-6 High 6. Donations The development of XDAGJ is inseparable from the support of XDAG fans. I hope you will continue to support the development and testing of XDAGJ, and the developer team will return to the society with excellent code.[https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj#sponsorship]. As well you can also fund our main development wallets at this adress : XDAG: FQglVQtb60vQv2DOWEUL7yh3smtj7g1s BTC: 39QyFnyoW45dWMReaZtcoRHP2S4DqU8xQG ETH: 0xb5F34fEb083186AfcB1DB1eFdE41eDA1f9BD9fB1 7. Bug bounty After the XDAGJ testnet went live, in order to encourage community enthusiasts to participate in the construction of XDAGJ, a bug bounty hunter activity was launched. If you find a bug, please visit[https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/issues/new/choose] Submit a bug and leave your XDAG address. After we review, we will reward 1000XDAG to this address if a bug is found. 8. Conclusion Currently, XDAG has initially entered a stage of benign development. On the one hand, the Mars project plans the future development path of XDAG, gathers community forces, and promotes the evolution of XDAG to a new height; on the other hand, it uses the world’s number one Java programming language to improve the XDAG ecosystem, attract developers to join, and grow with the future king. Finally a prosperous scene of XDAG will be realized. The Mars project will also hold a number of activities to interact with XDAG fans, so stay tuned. -By XDAG Community</summary></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAGJ v0.4.0 Testnet</title>
      <link href="/2021/04/27/XDAG-Java-Testnet-Tutorial.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAGJ v0.4.0 Testnet" />
      <published>2021-04-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2021-04-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2021/04/27/XDAG-Java-Testnet-Tutorial</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/27/XDAG-Java-Testnet-Tutorial.html">Hello to all,
As some of you know, we are currently working on making the project more attractive to developers.
In order to speed up the extension of the XDAG project as much as possible.
That’s why we have been promoting the development of the java version lately, and we now have a much healthier testing environment than before.
We need you to test this test network and the tools that go with it.

After finding a problem with TestNet, users can submit feedback (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/issues) and after confirming it as a valid bug, the bug finder will be rewarded with 1000 XDAG.

XDAG Java Edition Testing Tutorial

Full tutorial for testing XDAG Java Edition (Linux, MAC OS, Windows).

(https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/blob/master/docs/XDAGJ_TestNet_Access_Turial_zh.md )
Tip: Please use the test network wallet for testing and store the main network wallet separately from the test network wallet to avoid confusion.

I. Test wallet

1. Download the XDAG TestNet Wallet (Windows version)
(https://github.com/swordlet/win-wallet/releases/tag/0.4.0)
After downloading and unpacking, run XDagWallet.exe, to distinguish the main network wallet users will have the words “Test Network XDAG Wallet” on the interface (test wallets do not need to modify the configuration, has been automatically set to link the test network).

2. Users can use the test wallet for normal operations such as transferring funds, making notes, history, checking balance, etc. If you find any problems in the process, please provide feedback in time.

3. Test coins can be obtained by mining (after the test wallet is linked to the mining pool, it will also obtain some XDAG).

II. Test mining

1. Download the mining software and unzip the file
(https://github.com/XDagger/XdagRandomxMiner/releases/download/0.4.1/Release_win_x64_0.4.1.zip)

2. Set the “Locked memory page”
as required and restart the computer, details: (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/blob/master/docs/Win10_Configuration_RandomX_Algorithm_Environment_zh.md)

3. Start the mining command
DaggerMiner.exe -cpu -T -p  -t  -a 
Example (please change the address to XDAG personal test address): DaggerMiner.exe -cpu -T -p 1.15.78.91:9992 -t 2 -a +ZPRYegKvBUNi6I+xlxz+U+IP0QzCBkg (Hint: the wallet address of the main network and the test network are not common, please fill in the test network wallet address)

III.Test network blockchain browser

Users can check the address balance, transfer records and other related information through the test network blockchain browser (http://146.56.240.230/).

IV. Reward
After finding a problem with TestNet, users can submit feedback (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/issues) and after confirming it as a valid bug, the bug finder will be rewarded with 1000 XDAG.

V. Community Support
After more than a year of development work by community contributors, the XDAG Java public beta version has been officially released recently, which is a masterpiece of craftsmanship. In order to attract more developers, we are asking the whole community to help increase the interest in the XDAG Java codebase to raise the buzz and attract more developers!

Method (just lift a finger).


  Open the link to (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj)
  Click on the “star” button below to follow the XDAG Java code base (requires registration on github).




Thanks to the community for their support!</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello to all, As some of you know, we are currently working on making the project more attractive to developers. In order to speed up the extension of the XDAG project as much as possible. That’s why we have been promoting the development of the java version lately, and we now have a much healthier testing environment than before. We need you to test this test network and the tools that go with it. After finding a problem with TestNet, users can submit feedback (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/issues) and after confirming it as a valid bug, the bug finder will be rewarded with 1000 XDAG. XDAG Java Edition Testing Tutorial Full tutorial for testing XDAG Java Edition (Linux, MAC OS, Windows). (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/blob/master/docs/XDAGJ_TestNet_Access_Turial_zh.md ) Tip: Please use the test network wallet for testing and store the main network wallet separately from the test network wallet to avoid confusion. I. Test wallet 1. Download the XDAG TestNet Wallet (Windows version) (https://github.com/swordlet/win-wallet/releases/tag/0.4.0) After downloading and unpacking, run XDagWallet.exe, to distinguish the main network wallet users will have the words “Test Network XDAG Wallet” on the interface (test wallets do not need to modify the configuration, has been automatically set to link the test network). 2. Users can use the test wallet for normal operations such as transferring funds, making notes, history, checking balance, etc. If you find any problems in the process, please provide feedback in time. 3. Test coins can be obtained by mining (after the test wallet is linked to the mining pool, it will also obtain some XDAG). II. Test mining 1. Download the mining software and unzip the file (https://github.com/XDagger/XdagRandomxMiner/releases/download/0.4.1/Release_win_x64_0.4.1.zip) 2. Set the “Locked memory page” as required and restart the computer, details: (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/blob/master/docs/Win10_Configuration_RandomX_Algorithm_Environment_zh.md) 3. Start the mining command DaggerMiner.exe -cpu -T -p -t -a Example (please change the address to XDAG personal test address): DaggerMiner.exe -cpu -T -p 1.15.78.91:9992 -t 2 -a +ZPRYegKvBUNi6I+xlxz+U+IP0QzCBkg (Hint: the wallet address of the main network and the test network are not common, please fill in the test network wallet address) III.Test network blockchain browser Users can check the address balance, transfer records and other related information through the test network blockchain browser (http://146.56.240.230/). IV. Reward After finding a problem with TestNet, users can submit feedback (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj/issues) and after confirming it as a valid bug, the bug finder will be rewarded with 1000 XDAG. V. Community Support After more than a year of development work by community contributors, the XDAG Java public beta version has been officially released recently, which is a masterpiece of craftsmanship. In order to attract more developers, we are asking the whole community to help increase the interest in the XDAG Java codebase to raise the buzz and attract more developers! Method (just lift a finger). Open the link to (https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj) Click on the “star” button below to follow the XDAG Java code base (requires registration on github). Thanks to the community for their support!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/mmexport1619538583244.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG Rebranding result</title>
      <link href="/2021/04/18/Rebranding-result.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG Rebranding result" />
      <published>2021-04-18T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2021-04-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2021/04/18/Rebranding-result</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/18/Rebranding-result.html">Hello everyone

Marketing
The votes are closed since a while, it’s time to unveil what will be the new logo of the XDAG project:



The refresh of our old logo wins the most votes, we will soon unveil the redesign of our website and our various pages on social networks.

You can download the logos by following this link: https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1w_Q-eAfGHHwUuEyGAyMIkAx9w92MZ4h3?usp=sharing

Technical
A new XDAGJ 0.4.1 release recently, and our devs are still working on adding Libp2p instead of DNET to increase the number of users, and to allow our network to grow as it should.

Randomx has really breathed new life into us by bringing in new miners and customers, which strengthens our network, and our presence, which has been felt on the prices over the last few days.
We are still a long way from what XDAG can become in the future, but we are really starting to see things more clearly, and developments are now moving at a good pace.

Exchange
We are still working on getting in touch with new exchanges to get listed, we will come back to you soon with fresh news on this subject.</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello everyone Marketing The votes are closed since a while, it’s time to unveil what will be the new logo of the XDAG project: The refresh of our old logo wins the most votes, we will soon unveil the redesign of our website and our various pages on social networks. You can download the logos by following this link: https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1w_Q-eAfGHHwUuEyGAyMIkAx9w92MZ4h3?usp=sharing Technical A new XDAGJ 0.4.1 release recently, and our devs are still working on adding Libp2p instead of DNET to increase the number of users, and to allow our network to grow as it should. Randomx has really breathed new life into us by bringing in new miners and customers, which strengthens our network, and our presence, which has been felt on the prices over the last few days. We are still a long way from what XDAG can become in the future, but we are really starting to see things more clearly, and developments are now moving at a good pace. Exchange We are still working on getting in touch with new exchanges to get listed, we will come back to you soon with fresh news on this subject.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/LOGO-01-2.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG Rebranding</title>
      <link href="/2021/04/07/Rebranding-vote.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG Rebranding" />
      <published>2021-04-07T08:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2021-04-07T08:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2021/04/07/Rebranding-vote</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/07/Rebranding-vote.html">Logo psd created by customscene - www.freepik.com

XDAG Rebranding

As we enter a new phase of development, a member of the community with a certain talent for graphic design has proposed to create a new identity for us as well as a redesign of our publication media (website/social media…).
That’s why we would like to submit to the vote of the community the new graphic identity to adopt for the future, starting with the logo.

There are 6 distinct logos that you can consult in the attached pdf, the first being a rebranding of our current logo, accompanied by 5 other proposals.

For this vote we will again use the wallet system with 1 XDAG = 1 vote, the wallet with the most XDAGs wins.

Here are the 6 wallet addresses, from 1 to 6 according to the order of the pdf.


  OpWDV70/zKvWPbfDCBvNP+5jJkYMUU58
  N7qug+TQUUbtMlY+LcZBQZiSpJoqevmL
  iDbvXS84km4widnAfhcuz/2YzsRRVHeh
  jwEfsbIUG4rNJ1pCZh+jKCyim4AHoQYv
  RC2m//hv2mUxx5NfvLkJT1t56w6VTKMY
  U3AQzfxFb0Zr78XuYaBKvJjV0Oja2MCg


Here is the pdf with the different logos : https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ILZepVX-2i7NmamfhH6aYy0X5WWcXmnu/view?usp=sharing

Voting ends on Sunday, Apr 11th 2021.

All funds collected by vote will be donated to the development fund.
For any donation to the designer, we created a specific task for it, community as well will cover half of the target.</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">Logo psd created by customscene - www.freepik.com XDAG Rebranding As we enter a new phase of development, a member of the community with a certain talent for graphic design has proposed to create a new identity for us as well as a redesign of our publication media (website/social media…). That’s why we would like to submit to the vote of the community the new graphic identity to adopt for the future, starting with the logo. There are 6 distinct logos that you can consult in the attached pdf, the first being a rebranding of our current logo, accompanied by 5 other proposals. For this vote we will again use the wallet system with 1 XDAG = 1 vote, the wallet with the most XDAGs wins. Here are the 6 wallet addresses, from 1 to 6 according to the order of the pdf. OpWDV70/zKvWPbfDCBvNP+5jJkYMUU58 N7qug+TQUUbtMlY+LcZBQZiSpJoqevmL iDbvXS84km4widnAfhcuz/2YzsRRVHeh jwEfsbIUG4rNJ1pCZh+jKCyim4AHoQYv RC2m//hv2mUxx5NfvLkJT1t56w6VTKMY U3AQzfxFb0Zr78XuYaBKvJjV0Oja2MCg Here is the pdf with the different logos : https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ILZepVX-2i7NmamfhH6aYy0X5WWcXmnu/view?usp=sharing Voting ends on Sunday, Apr 11th 2021. All funds collected by vote will be donated to the development fund. For any donation to the designer, we created a specific task for it, community as well will cover half of the target.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/rebranding.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG Fork for RandomX deployment</title>
      <link href="/2021/02/18/RandomX-Fork.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG Fork for RandomX deployment" />
      <published>2021-02-18T16:35:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2021-02-18T16:35:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2021/02/18/RandomX-Fork</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/18/RandomX-Fork.html">XDAG Fork for RandomX deployment

As warned some days ago, RandomX will go live on our mainnet on main block 1540096 February 22nd 2021, 15:00 UTC .
There will be no changes or manipulations to be made for the users, only the mining pools are concerned.
We will come back to you with an update of the wallets shortly.

Mining changes

As you all know, this change of algo was long overdue to counter the big miners who were taking over the network.
From now on, anyone can mine XDAG, even from his or her desktop computer.
This opens up a wide field of possibilities for mining, and we hope to convince the mining communities of Monero and Firo to join us to strengthen our network.

Technical

We already have a miner ready for use, there are no major changes other than the algo.

This miner does not require files wallet.dat and dnet_key.dat. Storage folder is still necessary.

You can find it at this adress: https://github.com/XDagger/XdagRandomxMiner/releases/tag/v0.4</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">XDAG Fork for RandomX deployment As warned some days ago, RandomX will go live on our mainnet on main block 1540096 February 22nd 2021, 15:00 UTC . There will be no changes or manipulations to be made for the users, only the mining pools are concerned. We will come back to you with an update of the wallets shortly. Mining changes As you all know, this change of algo was long overdue to counter the big miners who were taking over the network. From now on, anyone can mine XDAG, even from his or her desktop computer. This opens up a wide field of possibilities for mining, and we hope to convince the mining communities of Monero and Firo to join us to strengthen our network. Technical We already have a miner ready for use, there are no major changes other than the algo. This miner does not require files wallet.dat and dnet_key.dat. Storage folder is still necessary. You can find it at this adress: https://github.com/XDagger/XdagRandomxMiner/releases/tag/v0.4</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/randomXdag.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG RandomX Deployement</title>
      <link href="/2021/02/11/RandomX-depoiement.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG RandomX Deployement" />
      <published>2021-02-11T01:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2021-02-11T01:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2021/02/11/RandomX-depoiement</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/11/RandomX-depoiement.html">The community is happy to announce that according to the Apollo program planning, after the developer’s unremitting efforts, the new mining algorithm of XDAG is now ready.
We’ll release a new version and switch to the new algorithm (RandomX) online in the near future.
At the same time, the 300,000 XDAGs from the initial crowdfunding will be awarded to the relevant contributors (https://xdag.io/task#community )

The new algorithm will bring the following advantages to the community:

1. The new algorithm will first support CPU mining, which will solve the problem of XDAG mining fairness.
2. The new algorithm will attract more miners to join as it become easier to mine and the growing team of miners will greatly improve the stability of the XDAG network.

Thank you for the support of the community members, and we wish to all of our Chinese community a happy Chinese New Year and XDAG bullishness!</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">The community is happy to announce that according to the Apollo program planning, after the developer’s unremitting efforts, the new mining algorithm of XDAG is now ready. We’ll release a new version and switch to the new algorithm (RandomX) online in the near future. At the same time, the 300,000 XDAGs from the initial crowdfunding will be awarded to the relevant contributors (https://xdag.io/task#community ) The new algorithm will bring the following advantages to the community: 1. The new algorithm will first support CPU mining, which will solve the problem of XDAG mining fairness. 2. The new algorithm will attract more miners to join as it become easier to mine and the growing team of miners will greatly improve the stability of the XDAG network. Thank you for the support of the community members, and we wish to all of our Chinese community a happy Chinese New Year and XDAG bullishness!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/xdaglaptop.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG November Monthly Report</title>
      <link href="/2020/11/28/XDAG-Monthly-Report.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG November Monthly Report" />
      <published>2020-11-28T12:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2020-11-28T12:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2020/11/28/XDAG-Monthly-Report</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2020/11/28/XDAG-Monthly-Report.html">A NEW BEGINNING (FRESH START)

It’s a season of new dawn and great progress for us all in XDAG community,

We’re glad that gradually our strategy and plan that is engineered are beginning to actualize in real-time.

Day in day out’ as a community project having large support from people who are enthusiast of this great project has been of great immense help and part of what keeps all going.

We appreciate everyone support.

Exchange Listing



We’re glad to be listed on CoinEx as we made the official announcement of the listing on  26th of November 2020,  trading activities already started with a XDAG/USDT Pair.

We’ve been in top gainers on arrival :



Here is the link to the announcement: » Announcement «

Technical Update

Our next release 0.4.0 is still in review, we really miss more dev to watch our code, the more we are, faster development will goes forward.
Random X last stage is now completed, but still under review to avoid ambiguities,It will be deployed in our 0.5.0 rev.

Marketing and community

More marketing strategy are already in place, we will be having upcoming Community AMA Series and also more promption campaign in the future, announcements regarding this will be communicated at the right time. 
We worked also to update all website where our stats and metrics are displayed, so CoinmarketCap/coinguecko and coinpaprika at least should display good information now.

Our community users based are increasing daily, happy to see more enthusiast are joining XDAG community, and they also have their slogan saying they are “Proudly Xdagian” we’re also proud of your continued support and contribution.

Lastly this report won’t be complete without adding the most recent and informative AMA we just did in the CoinEx community, Titled “Walk into the originator of [DAG+POW] XDAG” 
It was a mind blowing session, kindly see the link to check out the Recap :

» AMA Recap «

In conclusion we are still in pursuit of bringing Unique technologies for all and making sure XDAG stand out admist all, together we can make it possible, more goodnews will still be shared in the community.</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">A NEW BEGINNING (FRESH START) It’s a season of new dawn and great progress for us all in XDAG community, We’re glad that gradually our strategy and plan that is engineered are beginning to actualize in real-time. Day in day out’ as a community project having large support from people who are enthusiast of this great project has been of great immense help and part of what keeps all going. We appreciate everyone support. Exchange Listing We’re glad to be listed on CoinEx as we made the official announcement of the listing on 26th of November 2020, trading activities already started with a XDAG/USDT Pair. We’ve been in top gainers on arrival : Here is the link to the announcement: » Announcement « Technical Update Our next release 0.4.0 is still in review, we really miss more dev to watch our code, the more we are, faster development will goes forward. Random X last stage is now completed, but still under review to avoid ambiguities,It will be deployed in our 0.5.0 rev. Marketing and community More marketing strategy are already in place, we will be having upcoming Community AMA Series and also more promption campaign in the future, announcements regarding this will be communicated at the right time. We worked also to update all website where our stats and metrics are displayed, so CoinmarketCap/coinguecko and coinpaprika at least should display good information now. Our community users based are increasing daily, happy to see more enthusiast are joining XDAG community, and they also have their slogan saying they are “Proudly Xdagian” we’re also proud of your continued support and contribution. Lastly this report won’t be complete without adding the most recent and informative AMA we just did in the CoinEx community, Titled “Walk into the originator of [DAG+POW] XDAG” It was a mind blowing session, kindly see the link to check out the Recap : » AMA Recap « In conclusion we are still in pursuit of bringing Unique technologies for all and making sure XDAG stand out admist all, together we can make it possible, more goodnews will still be shared in the community.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/photo_2020-11-28_15-07-19.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG Monthly Report</title>
      <link href="/2020/11/01/Monthly-report.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG Monthly Report" />
      <published>2020-11-01T08:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2020-11-01T08:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2020/11/01/Monthly-report</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2020/11/01/Monthly-report.html">We’re Almost There!

October has been a great month for XDAG community, awesome growth in our Telegram and twitter community.
 We’re glad to have an increased number of community supporters, it’s showing more users and prospects are getting to know and ready to adopt XDAG. 
 We just want you to know that, we appreciate your support and commitment.



Exchange Listing

We’re still in talks with several exchanges so xdag can be listed, since we all know a new exchange is what all our community wants. Hopefully we get good feedback from them.

Technical Update

XDAG’s BIP44 universal code is 586!

Thanks to the efforts of community enthusiasts, XDAG now finally has its own BIP44 cointype 586!

So what is the BIP44? Why does XDAG need BIP44?
 To understand BIP44 we have to mention the HD wallet. Since there are so many cryptocurrencies nowadays and they are not easy to manage when one user has too many private keys, the HD wallet was created, and its function is that one master private key can generate multiple sub-private keys, that is, one HD wallet can be used to manage multiple cryptocurrency accounts and only one master private key needs to be backed up, and when the user has multiple blockchain assets (BTC, ETH, XDAG, etc.), the user can manage them in one HD wallet, this is much more convenient. 
BIP44 is the standard private key management protocol used by HD wallets, XDAG has now joined the BIP44 protocol with a common standard code so that HD wallets can support the management of XDAG address accounts.

Obtaining this standard code will facilitate further alignment of XDAG with BTC and ETH, which has many potential benefits for the future development of XDAG:

  Enables multi-chain wallets to support XDAG
  Enables XDAG to back up private key files using mnemonics.
  Facilitate professional teams to manage XDAG wallet hierarchically.


RandomX

Random X development is done, when it is fully reviewed we are going to launch it with the next update.



Briefly let talk about the “October effect” Bitcoin’s apparent effect has given more impression to still be the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization and daily trading volume. 
Xdag also hit a new ATH price up too in the month of October, which is a very great edge for the community, we’re almost there, it’s only a matter of time XDAG adoption will surely be global.

We remain committed, focused and as a community project with you all continuous support we’re going to have the XDAG of our dream.</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">We’re Almost There! October has been a great month for XDAG community, awesome growth in our Telegram and twitter community. We’re glad to have an increased number of community supporters, it’s showing more users and prospects are getting to know and ready to adopt XDAG. We just want you to know that, we appreciate your support and commitment. Exchange Listing We’re still in talks with several exchanges so xdag can be listed, since we all know a new exchange is what all our community wants. Hopefully we get good feedback from them. Technical Update XDAG’s BIP44 universal code is 586! Thanks to the efforts of community enthusiasts, XDAG now finally has its own BIP44 cointype 586! So what is the BIP44? Why does XDAG need BIP44? To understand BIP44 we have to mention the HD wallet. Since there are so many cryptocurrencies nowadays and they are not easy to manage when one user has too many private keys, the HD wallet was created, and its function is that one master private key can generate multiple sub-private keys, that is, one HD wallet can be used to manage multiple cryptocurrency accounts and only one master private key needs to be backed up, and when the user has multiple blockchain assets (BTC, ETH, XDAG, etc.), the user can manage them in one HD wallet, this is much more convenient. BIP44 is the standard private key management protocol used by HD wallets, XDAG has now joined the BIP44 protocol with a common standard code so that HD wallets can support the management of XDAG address accounts. Obtaining this standard code will facilitate further alignment of XDAG with BTC and ETH, which has many potential benefits for the future development of XDAG: Enables multi-chain wallets to support XDAG Enables XDAG to back up private key files using mnemonics. Facilitate professional teams to manage XDAG wallet hierarchically. RandomX Random X development is done, when it is fully reviewed we are going to launch it with the next update. Briefly let talk about the “October effect” Bitcoin’s apparent effect has given more impression to still be the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization and daily trading volume. Xdag also hit a new ATH price up too in the month of October, which is a very great edge for the community, we’re almost there, it’s only a matter of time XDAG adoption will surely be global. We remain committed, focused and as a community project with you all continuous support we’re going to have the XDAG of our dream.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/photo_2020-10-30_07-20-42.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en">
      <title type="html">XDAG Monthly Report</title>
      <link href="/2020/09/20/XDAG-Monthly-Report.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XDAG Monthly Report" />
      <published>2020-09-20T01:04:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2020-09-20T01:04:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/2020/09/20/XDAG-Monthly-Report</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/2020/09/20/XDAG-Monthly-Report.html">XDAG Monthly Report

At XDAG Community support makes XDAG grow stronger which we always acknowledge.

We just want to assure you that we have a lot of update that will be coming as we’re cooking up great things for the project. 
We are not here in the space for the hype but to give solution to the existing problem in the space and which we have not deviate from. 
We keep our focus on and surely we make the best.

In the past week the development ofXDAG had been progressive the developer are working on the product and how to make it a great success.

Twitter community contests

XDAG community launchs twitter daily check in activity, community members who successfully finish the activity will get 10000 XDAG each person (total 1 million XDAG, send by time sequence). Detailed rules:

  Send tweet daily, contents: #XDAG# day x. (x from 1 to 100)
  Tweets send 100 days fully.
Community members who meet the requirements, share your last tweet link and XDAG wallet address to @XDAG_Community, the rewards will be sent after confirmation.


JAVA IMPLEMENTATION

We just recently implement XDAGJ. 
XDAGJ is a Java implementation of XDAG. It is rebuilt on the basis of C Version XDAG. Kindly read full details on this link:
https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj

EXPLORER
Xdag explorer has just been updated you can view through this link: https://github.com/XDagger/explorer

Also the community just made a list of XDAG Wallet Rank of TOP100, you can check them out here:
https://xdag.io/rank#community

As you all know we offer a bleeding edge technology solution, let keep supporting xdag and we assure you that we will make you proud as the engine of cryptocurrency mass adoption is creating a big wave.</content><author>
          <name></name></author><summary type="html">XDAG Monthly Report At XDAG Community support makes XDAG grow stronger which we always acknowledge. We just want to assure you that we have a lot of update that will be coming as we’re cooking up great things for the project. We are not here in the space for the hype but to give solution to the existing problem in the space and which we have not deviate from. We keep our focus on and surely we make the best. In the past week the development ofXDAG had been progressive the developer are working on the product and how to make it a great success. Twitter community contests XDAG community launchs twitter daily check in activity, community members who successfully finish the activity will get 10000 XDAG each person (total 1 million XDAG, send by time sequence). Detailed rules: Send tweet daily, contents: #XDAG# day x. (x from 1 to 100) Tweets send 100 days fully. Community members who meet the requirements, share your last tweet link and XDAG wallet address to @XDAG_Community, the rewards will be sent after confirmation. JAVA IMPLEMENTATION We just recently implement XDAGJ. XDAGJ is a Java implementation of XDAG. It is rebuilt on the basis of C Version XDAG. Kindly read full details on this link: https://github.com/XDagger/xdagj EXPLORER Xdag explorer has just been updated you can view through this link: https://github.com/XDagger/explorer Also the community just made a list of XDAG Wallet Rank of TOP100, you can check them out here: https://xdag.io/rank#community As you all know we offer a bleeding edge technology solution, let keep supporting xdag and we assure you that we will make you proud as the engine of cryptocurrency mass adoption is creating a big wave.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/posts/xdagprogressreport.jpg" /></entry></feed>